{
    "quiz": {
        "hard": [
             {
                "question": "Amuse?",
                "options": [
                    "eğlendirmek",
                    "eğlence",
                    "eğlenmek",
                    "festival"
                ],
                "answer": "eğlendirmek"
            },
            {
                "question": "Balance?",
                "options": [
                    "orta",
                    "ayar",
                    "denge",
                    "dengelemek"
                ],
                "answer": "dengelemek"
            },
            {
                "question": "Chase?",
                "options": [
                    "kaçamak",
                    "kaçırmak",
                    "kovalamak",
                    "kaçmak"
                ],
                "answer": "kovalamak"
            },
            {
                "question": "Describe?",
                "options": [
                    "betimleme",
                    "tasvir",
                    "tanım",
                    "tanıtım"
                ],
                "answer": "tanım"
            },
            {
                "question": "Interrupt?",
                "options": [
                    "kesin",
                    "yarım",
                    "bölmek",
                    "yarıda kesmek"
                ],
                "answer": "yarıda kesmek"
            },
            {
                "question": "Prevent?",
                "options": [
                    "karşılamak",
                    "karşı gelmek",
                    "önüne geçmek",
                    "önlemek"
                ],
                "answer": "önlemek"
            }
        ],
        "medium": [
             {
                "question": "medium_Amuse?",
                "options": [
                    "eğlendirmek",
                    "eğlence",
                    "eğlenmek",
                    "festival"
                ],
                "answer": "eğlendirmek"
            },
            {
                "question": "Balance?",
                "options": [
                    "orta",
                    "ayar",
                    "denge",
                    "dengelemek"
                ],
                "answer": "dengelemek"
            },
            {
                "question": "Chase?",
                "options": [
                    "kaçamak",
                    "kaçırmak",
                    "kovalamak",
                    "kaçmak"
                ],
                "answer": "kovalamak"
            },
            {
                "question": "Describe?",
                "options": [
                    "betimleme",
                    "tasvir",
                    "tanım",
                    "tanıtım"
                ],
                "answer": "tanım"
            },
            {
                "question": "Interrupt?",
                "options": [
                    "kesin",
                    "yarım",
                    "bölmek",
                    "yarıda kesmek"
                ],
                "answer": "yarıda kesmek"
            },
            {
                "question": "Prevent?",
                "options": [
                    "karşılamak",
                    "karşı gelmek",
                    "önüne geçmek",
                    "önlemek"
                ],
                "answer": "önlemek"
            }
        ],
        "easy": [ {
                "question": "Sister?",
                "options": [
                    "kız kardeş",
                    "baba",
                    "amca",
                    "teyze"
                ],
                "answer": "kız kardeş"
            },

 {
                "question": "glass?",
                "options": [
                    "bardak",
                    "vazo",
                    "pencere",
                    "gözlük"
                ],
                "answer": "bardak"
            },
 {
                "question": "touch?",
                "options": [
                    "dokunmak",
                    "taç",
                    "kanape",
                    "acıkmak"
                ],
                "answer": "dokunmak"
            },
 {
                "question": "How?",
                "options": [
                    "Nasıl",
                    "Neden",
                    "Niçin",
                    "Niye"
                ],
                "answer": "Nasıl"
            },
 {
                "question": "october?",
                "options": [
                    "ekim",
                    " ocak",
                    "kasım",
                    "mayıs"
                ],
                "answer": "ekim"
            },
 {
                "question": "autumn?",
                "options": [
                    " kış",
                    "sonbahar",
                    " yaz",
                    "ilkbahar"
                ],
                "answer": "ilkbahar"
            },

 {
                "question": "thursday?",
                "options": [
                    "salı",
                    " perşembe",
                    "çarşamba",
                    "cuma"
                ],
                "answer": "perşembe"
            },

 {
                "question": "necklace?",
                "options": [
                    " kolye",
                    "eşarp",
                    "şort",
                    "terlik"
                ],
                "answer": " kolye"
            },

 {
                "question": "dress?",
                "options": [
                    "elbise",
                    "eldiven",
                    "bot",
                    "gömlek"
                ],
                "answer": "elbise"
            },

 {
                "question": "sheep?",
                "options": [
                    " koyun",
                    "kuzu",
                    "öküz",
                    " tavşan"
                ],
                "answer": "koyun"
            },

 {
                "question": "duck?",
                "options": [
                    "ördek",
                    "kaz",
                    "keçi",
                    "kaplumbağa"
                ],
                "answer": "ördek"
            },
{
                "question": "horse?",
                "options": [
                    "at",
                    "eşek",
                    "inek",
                    "boğa"
                ],
                "answer": "at"
            },
{
                "question": "lizard?",
                "options": [
                    "kertenkele",
                    "kaplumbağa",
                    "su yılanı",
                    "timsah"
                ],
                "answer": "kertenkele"
            },
{
                "question": "bear?",
                "options": [
                    "bira",
                    "panda",
                    "ayı",
                    "sakal"
                ],
                "answer": "ayı"
            },
{
                "question": "wolf?",
                "options": [
                    "kurt",
                    "köpek",
                    "baykuş",
                    "fil"
                ],
                "answer": "kurt"
            },
{
                "question": "scorpion?",
                "options": [
                    "tuna balığı",
                    "akrep",
                    "yılan",
                    "timsah"
                ],
                "answer": "akrep"
            },
{
                "question": "crocodile?",
                "options": [
                    "timsah",
                    "papağan",
                    "balina",
                    "ahtapot"
                ],
                "answer": "timsah"
            },
{
                "question": "dolphin?",
                "options": [
                    "ahtapot",
                    "balina",
                    "kartal",
                    "yunus"
                ],
                "answer": "yunus"
            },
{
                "question": "builder?",
                "options": [
                    "inşaatçı",
                    "bahçıvan",
                    "marangoz",
                    "kapıcı"
                ],
                "answer": "inşaatçı"
            },
{
                "question": "artist?",
                "options": [
                    "ressam",
                    "aktris",
                    "dansçı",
                    "aktör"
                ],
                "answer": "ressam"
            },
{
                "question": "nurse?",
                "options": [
                    "hemşire",
                    "itfaiyeci",
                    "dişçi",
                    "temizlikçi"
                ],
                "answer": "hemşire"
            },
{
                "question": "businessman?",
                "options": [
                    "iş adamı",
                    "avukat",
                    "otobüs şöförü",
                    "politikacı"
                ],
                "answer": "iş adamı"
            },
{
                "question": "sailor?",
                "options": [
                    "denizci",
                    "astronot",
                    "asker",
                    "satış görevlisi"
                ],
                "answer": "denizci"
            },



{
                "question": "lawyer?",
                "options": [
                    "avukat",
                    "mühendis",
                    "pilot",
                    "tesisatçı"
                ],
                "answer": "avukat"
            },



{
                "question": "lunch?",
                "options": [
                    "kahvaltı",
                    "öğle yemeği",
                    "akşam yemeği",
                    "gece acıkması"
                ],
                "answer": "öğle yemeği"
            },



{
                "question": "sand?",
                "options": [
                    "sandal",
                    "kum",
                    "tuz",
                    "kaya"
                ],
                "answer": "kum"
            },



{
                "question": "natural?",
                "options": [
                    "doğal",
                    "hızlı",
                    "pastorize",
                    "erken"
                ],
                "answer": "doğal"
            },



{
                "question": "wrong?",
                "options": [
                    "yanlış",
                    "genç",
                    "garip",
                    "özel"
                ],
                "answer": "yanlış"
            },



{
                "question": "warm?",
                "options": [
                    "ılık",
                    "solucan",
                    "bulunmak",
                    "koyu"
                ],
                "answer": "ılık"
            },
{
                "question": "kind?",
                "options": [
                    "çocuk",
                    "nazik",
                    "gevşek",
                    "önemli"
                ],
                "answer": "nazik"
            },
{
                "question": "regular?",
                "options": [
                    "düzenli",
                    "sessiz",
                    "mümkün",
                    "yasal"
                ],
                "answer": "düzenli"
            },

{
                "question": "strange?",
                "options": [
                    "garip",
                    "kalın",
                    "güçlü",
                    "sağlıklı"
                ],
                "answer": "garip"
            },
{
                "question": "broken?",
                "options": [
                    "parça",
                    "kırık",
                    "uyanık",
                    "kızgın"
                ],
                "answer": "kırık"
            },
{
                "question": "dark?",
                "options": [
                    "karanlık",
                    "kötü",
                    "ölü",
                    "farklı"
                ],
                "answer": "karanlık"
            },



{
                "question": "flat?",
                "options": [
                    "düz",
                    "yüksek ses",
                    "kuru",
                    "temiz"
                ],
                "answer": "düz"
            },
{
                "question": "ship?",
                "options": [
                    "rezarvasyon",
                    "gemi",
                    "çabuk",
                    "kuzu"
                ],
                "answer": "gemi"
            },

{
                "question": "street?",
                "options": [
                    "düz",
                    "sokak",
                    "cadde",
                    "şerit"
                ],
                "answer": "sokak"
            },
{
                "question": "boat?",
                "options": [
                    "tekne",
                    "bot",
                    "gemi",
                    "yelkenli"
                ],
                "answer": "tekne"
            },
{
                "question": "badly?",
                "options": [
                    "fena halde",
                    "yaklaşı",
                    "sabırla",
                    "kötüce"
                ],
                "answer": "fena halde"
            },
{
                "question": "differently?",
                "options": [
                    "farklı bir şekilde",
                    "akıcı bir biçimde",
                    "çoğunlukla",
                    "kesinlikle"
                ],
                "answer": "farklı bir şekilde"
            },
{
                "question": "hope?",
                "options": [
                    "umut",
                    "barış",
                    "huzur",
                    "mutluluk"
                ],
                "answer": "umut"
            },



{
                "question": "light?",
                "options": [
                    "ışık",
                    "fener",
                    "çakmak",
                    "dürbün"
                ],
                "answer": "ışık"
            },
{
                "question": "gun?",
                "options": [
                    "silah",
                    "mermi",
                    "ateş etmek",
                    "tetik"
                ],
                "answer": "silah"
            },
{
                "question": "wallet?",
                "options": [
                    "vestiyer",
                    "cüzdan",
                    "duvar boyası",
                    "led şeridi"
                ],
                "answer": "cüzdan"
            },
{
                "question": "nervous?",
                "options": [
                    "gergin",
                    "cesaret",
                    "nergis",
                    "sinirli"
                ],
                "answer": "gergin"
            },
{
                "question": "gloven?",
                "options": [
                    "eldiven",
                    "pipet",
                    "çatal",
                    "yüzük"
                ],
                "answer": "eldiven"
            },



{
                "question": "key?",
                "options": [
                    "anahtar",
                    "saat",
                    "çevir",
                    "takım"
                ],
                "answer": "anahtar"
            },



{
                "question": "shyly?",
                "options": [
                    "ahmakça",
                    "muhakkak",
                    "ürkekçe",
                    "akıcı"
                ],
                "answer": "ürkekçe"
            },



{
                "question": "window?",
                "options": [
                    "teras",
                    "pencere",
                    "masa",
                    "cam"
                ],
                "answer": "pencere"
            }
        ]
    }
}